question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, 'Chewbacca', is an Ewok.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "The movie 'The Nightmare before Christmas' was all done with physical objects.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "The film '2001: A Space Odyssey' was released on December 31st, 2000.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "The word 'Inception' came from the 2010 blockbuster hit 'Inception'.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "Shaquille O'Neal appeared in the 1997 film 'Space Jam'.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock's film 'Psycho' it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "question": "'Foodfight!' earned less than $80,000 at box office.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    }
]
